{"data":[{"question":"There are 28 pounds in _______.","a":"two stones","b":"two stone","c":"two-stone","d":"two-stones","answer":"2","explain":"\n- 1 stone = 6.35029318 kilograms \n- 1 pound = 453.59237 grams ","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"71","subcategorylv2":"3","type":"1"},{"question":"One pound is ________ ounces.","a":"16","b":"100","c":"101","d":"10","answer":"1","explain":"\n\n-1 pound = 453.59237 grams\n\n-1 ounce = 28.3495231 grams\n\n","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"71","subcategorylv2":"3","type":"1"},{"question":"_______ did you say that suitcase is?","a":"How heavy","b":"How weight","c":"What heavy","d":"What weight","answer":"1","explain":"\n- How heavy: how much does it weigh ","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"71","subcategorylv2":"3","type":"1"},{"question":"That American lady _______ 195 lbs.","a":"weights","b":"weighes","c":"weighs","d":"weightes","answer":"3","explain":"\n- Weigh(v): After singular third person: weighs","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"71","subcategorylv2":"3","type":"1"},{"question":"In the old days a cental was ________.","a":"10 kilos","b":"100 kilos","c":"50 pounds","d":"100 pounds","answer":"4","explain":"\n- Cental: a unit of weight equal to 100 pounds","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"71","subcategorylv2":"3","type":"1"},{"question":"A pint of milk is about ______.","a":"half a litre","b":"two litres","c":"sixteen litres","d":"four litres","answer":"1","explain":"\n- 1 US pint = 473.176473 millilitres\u00a0","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"71","subcategorylv2":"3","type":"1"},{"question":"If you buy a pound of sweets, you get ______ ounces.","a":"12","b":"14","c":"16","d":"18","answer":"3","explain":"\n-1 pound = 453.59237 grams \n-1 ounce = 28.3495231 grams ","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"71","subcategorylv2":"3","type":"1"},{"question":"A pint of beer is about ________.","a":"six litres","b":"four litres","c":"half a litre","d":"two litres","answer":"3","explain":"\n- 1 US pint = 473.176473 milliliters ","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"71","subcategorylv2":"3","type":"1"},{"question":"_______ are you?","a":"What heavy","b":"How heavy","c":"What weight","d":"How weight","answer":"2","explain":"\n- How heavy: how much does it weigh ","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"71","subcategorylv2":"3","type":"1"},{"question":"In the British Isles the average woman weighs about _______.","a":"ten stones","b":"ten stone","c":"forty stone","d":"eighty stones","answer":"2","explain":"- 1 stone = 6.35029318 kilograms\u00a0\n- The plural form of stone is correctly stone","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"71","subcategorylv2":"3","type":"1"}]}